Guide to the Joe Negri Collection, 1930-2014 CAM.JNC.2014
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Original Compositions, I.
  - Compositions with Bob McCully, 2.
    - "Give Love a Chance" (Box 8, Folder 580-586, Item 586)
      photostat of holograph manuscript. 3 pages.
    - "The IBM Girl" (Box 8, Folder 587-594, Item 587)
      Typed lyrics on onion skin.
      Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: The Establishment Needs Love Too 1969
    - [Untitled, first line "Down the way where the nights are gay", March 5, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 587-594, Item 587A)
      typed lyrics with handwritten notes.
    - "Plant a Radish" (Box 8, Folder 587-594, Item 588)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notations.
    - "Tell Her" (Box 8, Folder 587-594, Item 589)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten melody line.
    - "The Fels Naptha Song" (Box 8, Folder 587-594, Item 590)
    - "The Fels Naptha song" (Box 8, Folder 587-594, Item 590.1)
      photostat of holograph manuscript.
    - "South Hills Village Mall" (Box 8, Folder 587-594, Item 591)
      photocopy of typed script. 3 pages.
    - "[untitled, p. 2] (Box 8, Folder 587-594, Item 592)
      photocopy of typed show schedule, page 2 only. Starts with (13) Le Mont.
    - "Geriatrics" (Box 8, Folder 587-594, Item 593)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten music.
    - "Opening Number" (Box 8, Folder 587-594, Item 594)
      Typed script with handwritten notes. 2 pages.
    - "Dirty Old Men Need Love, Too", 1969 (Box 8, Folder 595-602, Item 595)
      Typed show order with handwritten changes and notes. 2 pages.
    - "Song Medley" (Box 8, Folder 595-602, Item 596)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten changes. Three pages.
    - "The Nude Look" (Box 8, Folder 595-602, Item 597)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notations. Two pages.
    - "Lawrence is a Grand Old Name" (Box 8, Folder 595-602, Item 598)
    - "Toyland Revisited" (Box 8, Folder 595-602, Item 600)
    - "Shakespeare Said It" (Box 8, Folder 595-602, Item 601)
    - "What's So Funny About That?" (Box 8, Folder 595-602, Item 602)
      Typed lyrics and script with handwritten notes. 3 pages.
    - "[How about a possible number...] (Box 8, Folder 603-612, Item 603)
      handwritten notes brainstorming song ideas.
      Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Can't Milk a Cow With a Wrench 1969
    - "Bruce" (Box 8, Folder 603-612, Item 604)
    - "Sex Education" (Box 8, Folder 603-612, Item 605)
      photocopy of typed lyrics. Two pages.
    - "You Can't Milk a Cow with a Wrench" (Box 8, Folder 603-612, Item 606)
      handwritten notes on green paper.
    - "Organized Religion" (Box 8, Folder 603-612, Item 607)
    - "Hell" (Box 8, Folder 603-612, Item 608)
    - "Inflation" (Box 8, Folder 603-612, Item 609)
      Typed script. One page.
    - "Pot-Pourri" (Box 8, Folder 603-612, Item 610)
      Typed script with handwritten notations.
    - Pete! (Box 8, Folder 603-612, Item 611)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notation. 2 pages.
    - "Opener" (Box 8, Folder 603-612, Item 612)
      Typed script. 3 pages.
    - "The Twelve Days of Christmas" (Box 8, Folder 613-622, Item 613)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notations. 2 pages.
    - "Tango" (Box 8, Folder 613-622, Item 614)
      handwritten show order with handwritten notes.
    - "You Can't Milk a Cow with a Wrench" (Box 8, Folder 613-622, Item 615)
      Typed script with handwritten notes.
    - "The Box" (Box 8, Folder 613-622, Item 616)
      Typed script with handwritten notation.
    - "Glenn Campbell" (Box 8, Folder 613-622, Item 616A)
    - "Mine Alone' (Box 8, Folder 613-622, Item 617)
      Typed script.
    - "Sex" (Box 8, Folder 613-622, Item 618)
    - "You Can't Milk a Cow with a Wrench" (Box 8, Folder 613-622, Item 619)
    - "Just One of Those Days" (Box 8, Folder 613-622, Item 620)
    - "The Crime Wave" (Box 8, Folder 613-622, Item 621)
    - "Gigglin' Gertie" (Box 8, Folder 613-622, Item 622)
      Typed lyrics
    - "Crest" (Box 8, Folder 623-631, Item 623)
    - "Explanation" (Box 8, Folder 623-631, Item 624)
    - "Logic and Illogic" (Box 8, Folder 623-631, Item 625)
    - "God, the Earth, and Man" (Box 8, Folder 623-631, Item 626)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notation. 3 pages.
    - "The Ways of Love" (Box 8, Folder 623-631, Item 627)
    - "Where Did the Time Go?" (Box 8, Folder 623-631, Item 628)
    - "Pity the Suburban Housewife" (Box 8, Folder 623-631, Item 629)
    - "Prolouge [sic] - Opener" (Box 8, Folder 623-631, Item 630)
    - "Samba de Vacca" (Box 8, Folder 623-631, Item 631)
    - "Is There Anyone Here That We Haven't Offended" (Box 9, Folder 632-642, Item 632)
      Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription:
      1974 McCully-Negri Lyrics & Comedy Material
    - "Knock-Knock" (Box 9, Folder 632-642, Item 633)
    - "Material for Is There Anyone We Haven't Offended" (Box 9, Folder 632-642, Item 634)
      Typed list of show order.
    - "What the Hell's Going On at the Pittsburgh Playhouse?" (Box 9, Folder 632-642, Item 637)
      Typed lyrics. One page.
    - "Tribute to the Multiplicity of Spouses" (Box 9, Folder 632-642, Item 638)
    - "The Pill" (Box 9, Folder 632-642, Item 640)
    - "Snow White" (Box 9, Folder 632-642, Item 641)
      Typed lyrics. 3 pages.
    - "Gigglin' Gertie" (Box 9, Folder 632-642, Item 642)
    - "The Always - Hungry Blues" (Box 9, Folder 643-649A, Item 643)
    - "Oakie-Doakie" (Box 9, Folder 643-649A, Item 644)
    - "Cops and Robbers" (Box 9, Folder 643-649A, Item 645)
    - "The Facts of Heaven" (Box 9, Folder 643-649A, Item 646)
    - "Tribute to the Multiplicity of Spouses" (Box 9, Folder 643-649A, Item 647)
    - "African Diet" (Box 9, Folder 643-649A, Item 648)
    - "What the Hell's Going on at the Pittsburgh Playhouse?" (Box 9, Folder 643-649A, Item 649)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notation.
    - [untitled notes] (Box 9, Folder 643-649A, Item 649A)
      handwritten notes on yellow paper.
    - "Is There Anyone We haven't Offended?" title page (Box 9, Folder 650-664, Item 650)
      Typed cover page.
      Contents assumed to be part of revue "Is There Anyone We Haven't Offended?"
    - "African Diet" (Box 9, Folder 650-664, Item 654)
    - "The Bumbershoot" (Box 9, Folder 650-664, Item 655)
    - "Love Is" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 672)
      Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Who Delt This Mess!
    - "Gossiping Grapevine (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 673)
    - "People Are No Damn Good" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 674)
      Typed script with handwritten notation. 3 pages.
    - "Someday Soon I'm Going to Make it Big" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 675)
      Typed script and lyrics. Two pages.
    - "Tentative Rundown" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 676)
      Typed show order. Two copies.
    - "Who Dealt This Mess?" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 677)
      Typed song lyrics with handwritten notes.
    - "Party Line" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 678)
      Computer typed script. Two pages.
    - "Ode to O'dea" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 679)
    - "We Fell in Love at a Karate School" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 680)
    - "The Status" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 681)
    - "Dirty Books" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 682)
    - "Bimini Isle" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 683)
    - "Show Biz" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 684)
      Typed script. Two pages.
    - "Who's Going to Save the Republican Party?" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 685)
    - "The Ledge" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 686)
    - "A Girl is a Girl is a Girl" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 687)
    - "Bobby Dylan Revisited" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 688)
    - "The Gloop-Maker" (Box 9, Folder 672-689, Item 689)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notes. Three pages.
    - "If Stephen Foster Had Tried to Sell His Songs Today" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 690)
      Script typed on onion skin. 4 pages.
    - "Pittsburgh is Pretty" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 691)
    - "Pittsburgh is Pretty" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 692)
    - "Wonder If" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 693)
    - "1980" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 694)
    - "Camp" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 695)
      Typed script and lyrics with handwritten notes. Three pages.
    - "Poets of America, Arise!" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 696)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notation. Two pages.
    - "The Marriage Counsellor [sic]" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 697)
      Typed script. Three pages.
    - "A Real Life Commercial" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 698)
    - "The Will" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 699)
    - "Passport to Oblivion" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 700)
      Typed script and lyrics. One page.
    - "The Old Casino" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 701)
    - "The Voice of the Pirates" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 702)
    - "Contact" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 703)
      Computer typed script. 2 pages.
    - "The Dynamic Duo" (Box 9, Folder 690-704, Item 704)
    - "Pills, Potions and sweet-smelling Lotions" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 705)
      Typed script and lyrics. 3 pages.
    - "The Complaint" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 706)
    - "The Wrestler" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 707)
      Typed script. 1 page.
    - "I was a Highschool Dropout" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 708)
    - "The Gay Blade" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 709)
    - "The Demonstrators" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 710)
    - "The Married Life" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 711)
    - "Who Dealt This Mess?" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 713)
      Typed list of show order with handwritten notes.
    - "What did we do with our nights and our evenings before television came along?" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 714)
      mimeographed typed script and lyrics. Three pages. stapled.
    - "They Hate Us" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 715)
    - "The Story of William Penn" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 716)
      Typed script with handwritten parts. 3 pages.
    - "Celebrity in the Audience" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 717)
    - "Airport" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 718)
      Typed cover page on onion skin.
    - "Judy - Ballad" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 719)
      Typed coverpage on onion skin.
    - "Shepherd and the Angel" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 721)
      Typed coverpage.
    - "The New Yorker Magazine" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 721)
      Typed script on onion skin paper.
    - "Opener" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 722)
    - "Max's Wife" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 723)
      Typed coversheet.
    - "Howard Johnson" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 724)
      typed coversheet on onion skin.
    - "Who Will Finish the Season?" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 725)
    - "Medley" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 726)
      Typed coversheet on onion skin.
    - "Suburbia" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 727)
      Typed cover sheet on onion skin.
    - "The Guru" (Box 9, Folder 705-728, Item 728)
      Typed script on onion skin. Pages 2 & 3 only.
    - "Opener" (Box 9, Folder 729-737, Item 729)
      Typed lyrics on onionskin. 1 page.
      Show - We Dialed the World & It was Busy - 1968 Scripts, blackouts
    - "We Dialed the World But it was Busy" (Box 9, Folder 729-737, Item 730)
      Typed show order. 2 pages.
    - "People Are No Damn Good" (Box 9, Folder 729-737, Item 732)
      Typed sketch and lyrics. 3 pages.
    - "We've Been There" (Box 9, Folder 729-737, Item 732)
      Typed sketch on onion skin. 7 pages.
    - "An Evening Without Zsa Zsa Gabor" (Box 9, Folder 729-737, Item 733)
    - "Prologue" (for Evening Without Zsa Zsa Gabor) (Box 9, Folder 729-737, Item 734)
      Typed script on onion skin. 3 pages.
    - "It's Magic" (Box 9, Folder 729-737, Item 735)
      Photocopy of typed lyrics with handwritten notations. 2 pages.
    - "The Playmate of the Month" (Box 9, Folder 729-737, Item 735)
    - "Where would You Like to Eat?" (Box 9, Folder 729-737, Item 737)
    - "Who's Got the Habit?" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 738)
      Typed lyrics and script. 3 pages.
    - "Jeff Runs a Race" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 739)
      Typed story. 1 page.
    - "Poem" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 740)
      Typed poem. 1 page.
    - "Try to Remember" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 741)
    - "Taking Ghandi from a Baby" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 742)
      Typed sketch. 1 page.
    - "Crime Does Not Pay" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 743)
    - "School Days" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 744)
    - "The Gay Blade" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 745)
    - "The Defense Rests" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 746)
    - "Surprise! Surprise! (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 747)
    - "Car Rental" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 749)
    - "A Celebrity in the Crowd" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 750)
    - "Candy" (Box 9, Folder 738-752, Item 751)
    - "Our Favorite Candidate" (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 753)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notes. 1 page.
    - "The South Hills Village Mall" (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 754)
      Typed script with handwritten notations. 2 pages.
    - "Modern Nursery Rhymes" (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 755)
    - "William Tell Revisited" (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 756)
    - "The Incident on the 17th Floor" (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 757)
      Typed script. 2 pages.
    - "The Complaint" (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 758)
    - "Our Favorite Candidate" (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 759)
    - "Feet of Clay" (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 760)
    - "The Guru" (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 761)
    - "Suggested Titles for Show" (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 762)
      Typed list of potential show titles.
    - "Modern Nursery Rhymes" (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 763)
    - [untitled drawing] (Box 9, Folder 753-763A, Item 763A)
      untitled drawing of man on notebook paper.
    - "Pittsburgh's Not a Provincial Town" (Box 9, Folder 764-767, Item 764)
      Photocopy of typed script with notations. 2 pages.
      1974 Opening Songs ---------------- Lead Sheets & Lyrics
    - "Pittsburgh is Pretty" (Box 9, Folder 764-767, Item 764A)
      Photocopy of typed lyrics. 1 page.
    - "Pittsburgh is a Beautiful Town" (Box 9, Folder 764-767, Item 765)
    - "Night and the City" (Box 9, Folder 764-767, Item 766)
    - "Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania" (Box 9, Folder 764-767, Item 767)
    - "Opening Medley" (Box 9, Folder 768-775, Item 768)
    - "Opening" (Box 9, Folder 768-775, Item 769)
    - "In the Audience Tonight" (Box 9, Folder 768-775, Item 770)
    - "Who's in Charge of this Ratrace? (Opener)" (Box 9, Folder 768-775, Item 771)
      Photocopy of typed lyrics with handwritten notes. 1 page.
    - "Opening Number - Page 2" (Box 9, Folder 768-775, Item 771A)
      photocopy of typed script with handwritten changes. 1 page.
    - "Is There Anyone Here That We Haven't Offended" (Box 9, Folder 768-775, Item 772)
    - "Feet of Clay" (Box 9, Folder 768-775, Item 773)
    - "The World is Going Bananas" (Box 9, Folder 768-775, Item 774)
    - "Desdamona Fink" (Box 9, Folder 768-775, Item 775)
    - "Paper Mache" (Box 9, Folder 776-781, Item 776)
      Contents originally enclosed in manila folder with the following inscription: Special Material - Gossiping Grapevine Mot, Pie Ball, Etc.
    - "Moving Picture Ball" (Box 9, Folder 776-781, Item 777)
      Lyrics typed on onion skin. 2 pages.
    - "Hey, Look Me Over" (Box 9, Folder 776-781, Item 778)
    - "Gossiping Grapevine" (Box 9, Folder 776-781, Item 779)
      Typed lyrics. 4 pages. Stapled.
    - "Gossiping Grapevine" (Box 9, Folder 776-781, Item 780)
      Typed lyrics on onion skin. 4 pages.
    - "Hey, There" (Box 9, Folder 776-781, Item 781)
      Typed lyrics on onion skin. 1 page.
    - "Tell Him" (Box 9, Folder 782-786.2, Item 782)
      World's in a Sweat Jr. League Show - 1970 Night & the City Who's got the habit Beautiful People of Pgh Females of America Pills, Potions --
    - "Night & the City" (Box 9, Folder 782-786.2, Item 783)
      Holograph manuscript. Folio, two pages.
    - "Night and the City" (Box 9, Folder 782-786.2, Item 783.1)
    - "Joey" (Box 9, Folder 782-786.2, Item 784)
    - Pills, Potions, Lotion (Box 9, Folder 782-786.2, Item 785)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript. 3 pages. Page 3 is original, not photocopy.
    - "Who's Got the Habit" (Box 9, Folder 782-786.2, Item 786)
    - "Whose Got the Habit" (Box 9, Folder 782-786.2, Item 786.1)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 3 pages. 2 copies.
    - "Who's Got the Habit?" (Box 9, Folder 782-786.2, Item 786.2)
    - "Opening" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 789)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 4 pages.
      Cold shoulders & Hot Pants Beck's Revue -- (1971) Joe Negri & Bob McCully Cast Ted White Bob McCully David Spangler Judy Odea Winkie Miller Ann Leidick --------------------- Lead sheets - Lyrics - Sketches
    - "Ev'ryone is Somebody's Fool", May 24, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 790)
    - "Old Fashioned Corn", May 24, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 791)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 2 pages. 2 copies.
    - "What's the Matter with Good Old Fashioned Corn?" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 792)
    - "Cold Shoulders and Hot pants" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 793)
      Typed coverpage with cast listed and handwritten notes.
    - "Opening Talk" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 794)
    - "What's in the News? - (Opening)" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 795)
      Typed script of lyrics. Two pages.
    - "Gags" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 796)
    - "Henry J. Heinz" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 797)
    - "The Governor is a Five-Letter Word" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 798)
    - "Talkin' Coffin Blues" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 799)
    - "Whatta Ya Go?" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 800)
    - "Gigglin' Gertie" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 801)
    - "Moments" (Box 9, Folder 789-802, Item 802)
    - "The Patient" (Box 9, Folder 803-811, Item 803)
    - "Insomnia" (Box 9, Folder 803-811, Item 804)
    - "Henry J. Heinz" (Box 9, Folder 803-811, Item 805)
      Photocopy of typed script with handwritten notation. 3 pages.
    - "Talkin' Coffin Blues" (Box 9, Folder 803-811, Item 806)
    - "Happy Times" (Box 9, Folder 803-811, Item 807)
    - "The Governor is a Five-Letter Word" (Box 9, Folder 803-811, Item 808)
    - "The Good Old Days of Radio" (Box 9, Folder 803-811, Item 809)
    - "The Wonderful World of Crime" (Box 9, Folder 803-811, Item 810)
    - "Life's Little Pleasures" (Box 9, Folder 803-811, Item 811)
      Typed script. 4 pages. 2 copies.
    - "San Francisco Mornin'" (Box 9, Folder 812-818, Item 812)
    - "Life's Little Pleasures" (Box 9, Folder 812-818, Item 813)
    - "Moments" (Box 9, Folder 812-818, Item 814)
    - "Moments" (Box 9, Folder 812-818, Item 814.1)
    - "Moments" (Box 9, Folder 812-818, Item 814.2)
    - "Just Gotta Do It" (Box 9, Folder 812-818, Item 817)
    - "Worlds in a Sweat!" (Box 9, Folder 812-818, Item 818)
    - "Crossword" (Box 9, Folder 819-828, Item 819)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notes. 4 pages.
      Contents originally enclosed in a manila folder with the following inscription:
      Joe Negri - K.D.K.A. - T.V. Review Material ----------- "Live on Tape" ------------ ---------------------- Carrier's
    - "Don't Tempt Me" (Box 9, Folder 819-828, Item 820)
    - "Porto Bay" (Box 9, Folder 819-828, Item 821)
    - "Victim of Love" (Box 9, Folder 819-828, Item 822)
    - "I Found My Love" (Box 9, Folder 819-828, Item 823)
    - "Woman of Stone" (Box 9, Folder 819-828, Item 824)
    - "Wonder If" (Box 9, Folder 819-828, Item 825)
    - "When You Are Lonely" (Box 9, Folder 819-828, Item 826)
    - "Lisa" (Box 9, Folder 819-828, Item 827)
    - "The cure" (Box 9, Folder 819-828, Item 828)
      Typed lyrics with handwritten notes. 6 pages.
    - "Is There a Teabag in the House?" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 829)
      Joe Negri - K.D.K.A. - TV Review Material ----------- "Live on Tape" --------- ------------------------- Carrier's
    - "Just Fill Out the Form" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 830)
    - "Snow White" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 831)
    - "Good, Good, Good" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 832)
      Typed sketch on onion skin.
    - "One-Armed Driver" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 833)
      Typed script on onion skin. 1 page.
    - "David and Goliath" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 834)
      Script typed on onion skin. 1 page.
    - "Noah's Ark" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 835)
    - "It's Tragic" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 836)
      Typed script on onion skin. Two pages.
    - "Trouble" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 837)
      Typed lyrics on onion skin. Two pages.
    - "Opening" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 838)
    - "Opening" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 839)
    - "Tormented" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 840)
    - "Bachelor's Lament" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 841)
    - "Jolly Joe" coverpage (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 842)
    - "Briefly Encountered" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 843)
    - "Don't Tempt Me" (Box 9, Folder 829-844, Item 844)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript with handwritten notes.
    - "Story of Our Times" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 845)
      Title page written on staff paper.
    - "An Evening Without Zsa Zsa Gabor", 1962 (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 846)
      Title page with copyright notice.
    - "An Evening Without Zsa Zsa Gabor" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 847)
      Typed list of show order with handwritten notes. 1 page.
    - "Little Orphan Annie" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 848)
    - "Ralstontime" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 849)
    - "Live on Tape" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 851)
    - "Blackout" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 852)
    - "Opener" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 853)
      photocopy of holograph manuscript with handwritten changes. 2 pages.
    - "Close" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 854)
    - "It's Hell to be the Age You Are" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 855)
      holograph manuscript printed on onion skin. 1 page.
    - "City Slicker" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 856)
      Photocopy of holograph manuscript. 3 pages. Stapled.
    - "City Slicker The Spider and the Fly" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 856.1)
      typed lyrics with handwritten correction. 1 page.
    - "Triangle" (Box 9, Folder 845-857.1, Item 857)
      Holograph manuscript. Two-page folio.
    - "Excerpts from: An Evening Without Desdamona Fink" (Box 9, Folder 858-859, Item 859)
      Mimeographed script with handwritten notes. stapled.
      Contents originally enclosed in a manila folder with the following inscription: An Evening without Zsa Zsa Gabor.
  - Beck's Charter Oaks Shows, 3.
    Programs from Beck's Charter Oaks Shows
    - "An Evening Without Desdamona Fink", 1962 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1238)
      Photocopy of typed show order with handwritten notes. 1 page.
    - "400 Miles Off Broadway", 1964 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1239)
      Photocopy of printed program. 1 page.
    - "Desdamona Fink Meets the Son of Stagestruck", 1964 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1240)
    - "One Damn Thing After Another", 1964 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1244)
    - "Who's In Charge of this Ratrace?", 1965 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1242)
    - "Who Dealt This Mess?", 1966 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1243)
      Photocopy of printed program
    - "Is There Anyone We Haven't Offended?", 1967 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1244)
      photocopy of printed program.
    - "We Dialed the World, But It Was Busy", 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1245)
    - "The Establishment Needs Love, Too", 1969 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1246)
    - "You Can't Milk a Cow with a Wrench", 1970 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1247)
      Photocopy of printed program.
    - "Cold Shoulders and Hot Pants", 1971 (Box 13, Folder 1237-1251, Item 1248)